As I tie my laces up now I'm ready to go
Even the wind seems to push me forward
Using the light that shines through these kinds of doubt
Let's chase all of those dreams that were long forgotten
I can feel my heart racing with the beat
Mixed with feelings of doubt and looking ahead
Is everything really gonna be okay?
So can we really make it out the other side?
大丈夫だよ 見上げれば もう
大丈夫ほら 七色の橋
涙を流しきると 空に架かる
ねぇ見えるでしょ はるか彼方に
僕にも見える 君と同じの
二つの空が いま一つになる
やっと同じ空の下で 笑えるね
We were born under two totally different skies
Each star holds different memories for us
You have many stories that of course are all your own
And shed some tears that I don't know about
On a day when I was smiling and was so carefree
You could have been hurt or crying
We might have felt the same types of joy
But the hard times we had are all on our own
And all the promises we make to shape our future
We decorate with words of hopes in our dreams
You always hope for a better tomorrow
And I know more than anything or anyone else
巡る季節のひとつのように
悲しい時は 悲しいままに
幸せになることを 急がないで
大丈夫だよ ここにいるから
大丈夫だよ どこにもいかない
また走り出す時は 君といっしょ
If there was ever a world that had no tears
Would there even be a bridge to cross?
You tried everything you could to numb the pain
Afraid of getting wet from the rain
You tried to build a bridge by simply running away
From all the troubles that followed you
But now you throw away your umbrella
And simply close your eyes
(大丈夫)
大丈夫だよ 見上げれば もう
大丈夫ほら 七色の橋
涙を流し終えた君の空に
ねぇ見えるでしょ 色鮮やかに
僕にも見える 君と同じの
絆という名の虹が架かったね
そして 二つの空がやっと やっと 一つになって
僕らを走らせるんだ